thedailywellness.com 2014-09-21

# The Daily Wellness

Privacy Policy

Introduction

We are at The Daily Wellness are committed to protecting any data and information that we collect concerning you. By using our services and visiting our website, you agree to the use of your data that we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service and a pleasurable website viewing experience. This Policy indicates the type of data collection processes we utilize to collect data about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect such information and you hereby assent to its use thereof.

Information Collected

We may collect any or all of the information that you provide to us, depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

Information Use

We primarily use the information collected to process the task for which you visited our website. Data collected on our website is, and will be, held in accordance with applicable federal and state laws governing such information collection, dissemination and use. All reasonable precautions have been taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.

Cookies

Your Internet browser has the automatic feature of storing small files “cookies” that hold information that allows a website to recognise your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your website viewing experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired or eliminated all together.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

The DoubleClick DART (“DCD”) Cookie is a cookie that is used by Google and its affiliates to display certain Google AdSense advertisements. This website may use DCD Cookies from time to time. Whenever a user visits a partner’s website and either views or clicks on an advertisement, a cookie may be dropped into the end-user’s browser. The DCD Cookie helps Google target advertisements to you that you may find beneficial, based upon your previous browsing history. Third party vendors, such as Google, use DCD Cookies to serve ads to end users based on previous visits to our website. Google’s use of DCD Cookies enables Google, and others, to serve advertisements to you based on other sites you have visited on the Internet. If you do not wish to utilize the DCD Cookie, you may opt-out on our website.

Disclosing Information

We do not, and will not, disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction such as when arranging for a courier company to deliver goods that you have ordered. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will have the opportunity to remove yourself from any such mailing list or similar device. If, at any time in the future, we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.

We may, from time to time, provide information of a general nature to third parties for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.

Changes to this Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede and replace this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. It is strongly recommended, and encouraged, that you read this document each and every time you use, and visit, this website to ensure that it still meets your approval.

Children

Children must be at least thirteen (13) years of age before accessing this website. We do not solicit or encourage minors under the age of thirteen (13) to use our website.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please contact us anytime.
